<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Hitch Hiking</title>
    <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Go Hitch Hiking</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gohitchhiking.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> COZUMEL, 2023 - A Day of Adventure and Exploration</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-sargassum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-sargassum/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Cozumel, an enchanting island located off the coast of Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Yucatan Peninsula, is a hidden gem for those seeking adventure and relaxation. In this article, we will take you on a virtual tour of Cozumel in 2023, providing you with all the necessary information to plan your own exciting day trip to this tropical paradise.
Arriving in Cozumel To begin your day in Cozumel, you have two options for transportation from Playa Del Carmen: the Ultramar boat or the Windjet boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hawaii vs Costa Rica: Exploring Costa Rica&#39;s Incredible Wildlife</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hawaii-vs-costa-rica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hawaii-vs-costa-rica/</guid>
      <description>Overview In this article, we will be comparing the stunning wildlife of Hawaii and Costa Rica. As a first-time traveler, Lizette Sandoval from Louisville, Kentucky is torn between choosing Hawaii or Costa Rica as her next destination. We will provide detailed insights into why Costa Rica stands out when it comes to unique and diverse wildlife experiences.
Costa Rica: A Wildlife Paradise Costa Rica is renowned for its incredible biodiversity and is often referred to as a &amp;ldquo;wildlife paradise&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What to Know About Tulum Mexico: A Complete Guide to the Beautiful Destination</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-vs-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-vs-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Tulum, Mexico is a breathtakingly beautiful destination known for its stunning beaches, ancient ruins, and vibrant culture. In this article, we will explore everything you need to know about Tulum, from its history and attractions to where to stay and how to get there. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re planning a trip to this paradise on earth, keep reading!
The History and Culture of Tulum Tulum has a rich history that dates back to the ancient Mayan civilization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Police investigating brutal attack on man by group of teens on Anna Maria Island**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/anna-maria-island-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/anna-maria-island-crime/</guid>
      <description>Anna Maria Island has been hit with a shocking incident as a man was brutally beaten up by a group of teenagers while he was spending time with his niece. The incident has led to a police investigation, and authorities have identified some of the teens involved through surveillance video.
The victim, Evan Purcell, a 41-year-old resident of Anna Maria Island, was enjoying a day out with his ten-year-old niece at Anna Maria Elementary when they encountered the group of teenagers at the picnic tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs. Puerto Vallarta: Comparing the Best Sides of Mexico</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-vs-puerto-vallarta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-vs-puerto-vallarta/</guid>
      <description>Choosing between Puerto Vallarta and the Cancun side of Mexico can be a difficult decision. Both sides offer stunning features, but which is better for your vacation? In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll compare all the major highlights of Puerto Vallarta and the Cancun/Riviera Maya region to help you make the right choice.
The Best Side for an All-Inclusive Tropical Vacation If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a tropical all-inclusive vacation, Cancun is the better choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Living in Mexico: Isla Mujeres vs Tulum - A Weekend Getaway Guide</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/isla-mujeres-vs-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/isla-mujeres-vs-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore the popular tourist destinations of Isla Mujeres and Tulum in Mexico. Both locations offer unique experiences and attractions, making it difficult to choose between them for a weekend getaway. We will delve into the details of these two destinations, highlighting their key features, activities, and accommodations. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re interested in relaxing on pristine beaches or immersing yourself in vibrant nightlife, we&amp;rsquo;ll help you make an informed decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Punta Cana vs Cancun: A Comparison of Top Vacation Destinations</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cap-cana-vs-punta-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cap-cana-vs-punta-cana/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re in the process of planning your next vacation and can&amp;rsquo;t decide between Punta Cana and Cancun, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Both destinations offer stunning beaches, luxury resorts, and a plethora of activities for travelers to enjoy. In this article, we will delve into the similarities and differences of these two popular vacation spots, helping you make an informed decision for your upcoming trip.
1. All-Inclusive Resorts Both Punta Cana and Cancun are renowned for their abundance of all-inclusive resorts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Head-to-Head: Sarasota vs Naples Florida - Which Coastal Gem Should You Choose for Your New Home?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-far-is-sarasota-from-naples/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-far-is-sarasota-from-naples/</guid>
      <description>Are you considering a move to Florida and torn between the charming coastal towns of Sarasota and Naples? Look no further, as we compare these two popular destinations and help you decide which one is the perfect fit for you. In this article, we will delve into the key points and highlights of each city, allowing you to make an informed decision. So, let&amp;rsquo;s get started.
Sarasota, located on the Gulf Coast of Florida, is a city that offers a multitude of reasons to call it home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Seaweed Is Threatening the Pristine Beaches of Mexico&#39;s Riviera Maya</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/seaweed-in-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/seaweed-in-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Are you planning a trip to Cancun or the Riviera Maya? If so, there&amp;rsquo;s an important issue you should be aware of - the increasing problem of seaweed, specifically sargassum, that is plaguing the region&amp;rsquo;s beautiful beaches. In this article, we will provide you with a comprehensive update on the seaweed issue, explaining its causes, showcasing footage from various locations, and offering advice on how to navigate this growing concern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Title: Is Costa Rica Better Than Hawaii? Exploring the Top Reasons Americans Leave Costa Rica [Why I Left]</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-costa-rica-better-than-hawaii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-costa-rica-better-than-hawaii/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Many Americans dream of moving to Costa Rica for its stunning beaches, affordable living, and a laid-back lifestyle. However, not everyone who moves to this tropical paradise ends up staying. In this article, we will dive into the reasons why many Americans leave Costa Rica after a few years and the factors that contribute to their decision.
Expatriate Population in Costa Rica Costa Rica has become a popular destination for expatriates, particularly Americans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Seaweed Is Impacting Mexico&#39;s Pristine Beaches: Causes and Solutions</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/seaweed-cancun-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/seaweed-cancun-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Discover the extent of the seaweed or sargassum problem affecting the Riviera Maya region, and learn about its causes and potential solutions.
The Riviera Maya, located along the stunning coast of Mexico, has long been celebrated for its pristine beaches, crystal-clear waters, and breathtaking beauty. However, in recent years, a growing concern has emerged – the proliferation of seaweed, specifically sargassum, which is negatively impacting the region&amp;rsquo;s picturesque shores. In this article, we will delve into the causes behind this seaweed influx, explore the implications for travelers, and discuss potential solutions for mitigating this issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Destin Florida Vacation Guide: Discover the Best Ways to Save Money!</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/average-cost-to-vacation-in-destin-florida/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/average-cost-to-vacation-in-destin-florida/</guid>
      <description>Destin, Florida is widely regarded as one of the premier vacation spots in the state. In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into everything you need to know about this beautiful city, including the best times to visit, money-saving tips, recommended places to stay, top-rated restaurants, must-visit attractions, and more. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned traveler or a first-time visitor, this guide will ensure you make the most of your vacation in Destin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Playa Del Carmen Beach Seaweed Update: August 19th, 2023</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-there-still-seaweed-in-playa-del-carmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-there-still-seaweed-in-playa-del-carmen/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the latest sargasso update for Playa Del Carmen&amp;rsquo;s beaches. Today is Saturday, August 19th, 2023, and I have been providing these reports for over a year now. If you enjoy these updates, you can support me by visiting buy me a coffee.com 360. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the current state of the beaches.
Starting in Punta Esmeralda, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that August was historically one of the worst months for seaweed in this area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> San Antonio vs Austin: A Detailed Comparison</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/san-antonio-vs-austin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/san-antonio-vs-austin/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be comparing two prominent cities in Texas - San Antonio and Austin. Both cities have their own distinct characteristics and attractions, making it difficult to choose between them. We will delve into various aspects including population, housing, cost of living, and entertainment, to help you make an informed decision if you are considering a move to either of these cities.
Population When it comes to population, San Antonio takes the lead with a population of about 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why Isla Mujeres Must Be on Your Travel Bucket List</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/isla-mujeres-vs-cancun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/isla-mujeres-vs-cancun/</guid>
      <description>Isla Mujeres is a breathtaking Caribbean island located just off the coast of Cancun, Mexico. With its crystal clear waters and vibrant shades of turquoise and blue, this island is a paradise for travelers seeking an unforgettable beach getaway. In this article, we will take a closer look at Isla Mujeres and why it is a must-visit destination.
An Idyllic Setting As soon as you arrive on Isla Mujeres, the beauty of its surroundings will captivate you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs Cabo: Which Destination is Better for Your Vacation?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/maui-vs-cancun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/maui-vs-cancun/</guid>
      <description>Cancun and Cabo (Cabo San Lucas and San Jose del Cabo) have been popular vacation destinations since the 1960s. Both offer a wide range of experiences, including beautiful beaches, resort options, fun activities, and vibrant nightlife. However, each destination has its own unique strengths, making it important to choose the right one for your preferences. In this article, we will provide a detailed side-by-side comparison of Cancun and Cabo to help you make an informed decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Will Texas be Impacted by the Sargassum Seaweed Blob? A Detailed Analysis</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-free-destinations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-free-destinations/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Sargassum seaweed has been making headlines in the national media, sparking questions about its impact. In this article, we will explore the origins of sargassum seaweed, the reasons behind its recent proliferation, and whether or not it will affect Texas. Join ABC13 Houston&amp;rsquo;s chief meteorologist, Travis Herzog, as he explains the phenomenon and provides valuable insights.
The Origin of Sargassum Seaweed Sargassum seaweed originates from the Sargasso Sea, which is the only sea on the planet without any land boundaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs. Puerto Vallarta Mexico: Which Side is Better for Your Family Vacation?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cancun-or-puerto-vallarta-with-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cancun-or-puerto-vallarta-with-kids/</guid>
      <description>Deciding between Puerto Vallarta and the Cancun side of Mexico can be a difficult choice. Both sides offer stunning features that cater to different types of travelers. In this article, we will compare the major highlights of both destinations to help you determine whether Puerto Vallarta or the Cancun/Riviera Maya is a better fit for your family vacation.
Cancun: The Ultimate Tropical All-Inclusive Getaway If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a tropical, all-inclusive vacation, Cancun is the perfect destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Tulum Seaweed Ruining Your Beach Vacation? Exploring the Impact and Experience</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-seaweed-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-seaweed-january/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Tulum, known for its stunning beaches and crystal clear waters, is a popular vacation destination for travelers. However, in recent years, the presence of seaweed on the beaches has raised concerns among tourists. In this article, we will explore the current situation of seaweed in Tulum, how it affects the beach experience, and provide insights for planning your trip accordingly.
Tulum&amp;rsquo;s Seaweed Issue Tulum Beach is currently facing a significant influx of seaweed, unlike what many travelers may have experienced in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ocean Safety Guide: Protect Yourself on Kauai&#39;s Spectacular Beaches</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/kauai-beach-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/kauai-beach-safety/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the beautiful and breathtaking island of Kauai, where the beaches and oceans are truly magnificent. While they may seem like paradise, it&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that they can also be dangerous. In this article, we will discuss essential tips and guidelines to ensure your safety while enjoying Kauai&amp;rsquo;s beaches. We urge you to take a few moments to read this ocean safety guide so that you can have a safe and enjoyable visit to our island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Tulum vs Cozumel: Exploring Two Mexican Gems**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-vs-cozumel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-vs-cozumel/</guid>
      <description>Discover the beauty and allure of Tulum and Cozumel, two stunning destinations in Mexico
Mexico is home to many breathtaking destinations, but two that stand out are Tulum and Cozumel. These two gems offer unique experiences, from beautiful beaches to ancient ruins and vibrant culture. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re seeking relaxation or adventure, Tulum and Cozumel have something for everyone. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into what makes these destinations so special and help you decide which one is the perfect fit for your next vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Costa Rica vs. Puerto Rico: U17 Women&#39;s Basketball Championship 2023</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-versus-costa-rica/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-versus-costa-rica/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the U17 Women&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Center Championship, where two formidable teams, Costa Rica and Puerto Rico, are set to face off in an intense battle on the court. Both teams have shown immense potential and are determined to secure their first victory in the championship. This article will provide a detailed account of the game between Costa Rica and Puerto Rico, highlighting key players, strategies, and significant moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Punta Cana Seaweed Problem 2023: Will it Ruin Your Vacation?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cap-cana-seaweed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cap-cana-seaweed/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
When planning a tropical vacation, one usually dreams of clear blue waters and pristine, sandy beaches. However, in recent years, a new phenomenon has been threatening the idyllic image of Punta Cana, a popular tourist destination in the Dominican Republic. A massive seaweed blob, twice the width of the US, is making its way through the Atlantic Ocean and heading straight towards Punta Cana. This article will explore the seaweed problem and its potential impact on your vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Best Time to Visit Tybee Island: A Guide to Exploring this Beach Paradise</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/best-time-to-visit-tybee-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/best-time-to-visit-tybee-island/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
When it comes to discovering new places and embarking on exciting adventures, Tybee Island is a must-visit destination. Located just a quick 20-minute drive from historic Savannah, this picturesque island offers beautiful beaches, stunning sand dunes, and a laid-back atmosphere that makes it the perfect weekend getaway. In this article, we will explore the best things to do in Tybee Island, from renting a charming cottage to exploring its historic lighthouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Is Tulum Seaweed Ruining Your Beach Experience?**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-seaweed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-seaweed/</guid>
      <description>Tulum, a beautiful coastline in Mexico, is known for its stunning beaches and crystal-clear waters. However, recently, the presence of seaweed has sparked concerns among travelers. In this article, we will explore the current seaweed situation in Tulum and discuss whether it affects your beach vacation.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start by addressing the most common question: Can you still swim in the beach despite the seaweed? The answer is yes, you can still enjoy the water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Seaweed is Devastating Beaches in Playa del Carmen</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-algae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-algae/</guid>
      <description>Planning a trip to Cancun or the Riviera Maya? Think twice before expecting pristine beaches. The escalating issue of increased seaweed, known as sargassum, is turning Mexico&amp;rsquo;s beautiful beaches into a brown, smelly mess. In this article, we will explore the causes behind this problem, provide real-life footage of affected areas, and discuss potential solutions. Keep reading to understand the severity of the situation and how it may affect your visit to Playa del Carmen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> We Explored Cozumel, Isla Mujeres &amp; Holbox: A Comparison of Mexico&#39;s Popular Caribbean Islands</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-vs-isla-mujeres/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-vs-isla-mujeres/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be taking a closer look at three of the most popular islands in the Mexican Caribbean: Cozumel, Isla Mujeres, and Holbox. If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a trip to the Riviera Maya, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the unique qualities and attractions of each island in order to make an informed decision on which one to include in your travel itinerary. By comparing the size, transportation options, accommodation, beaches, and activities available on each island, we hope to provide you with the necessary information to choose the island that best suits your preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What&#39;s The Difference Between Miami and Miami Beach: Explained by a Real Estate Agent</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/palm-beach-vs-miami-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/palm-beach-vs-miami-beach/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you confused about the differences between Miami and Miami Beach? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. This question is frequently asked, especially by those who are not familiar with the area. However, as a local real estate agent in Miami and Miami Beach, I can shed some light on the subject. In this article, we will explore the distinctions between these two cities located in Miami-Dade County, Florida. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Guide to Safety and Attractions in Christiansted, St. Croix</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/christiansted-st-croix-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/christiansted-st-croix-safety/</guid>
      <description>Introduction St. Croix is a beautiful island with many attractions and activities to offer both locals and visitors. In this guide, we will explore the best of Christiansted, a twin city on the island known for its stunning Boardwalk, historic sites, delicious cuisine, and beautiful beaches. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a relaxing day by the sea, an adventurous horseback ride on the beach, or a taste of local Caribbean delicacies, Christiansted has something for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Chiang Mai Vs Chiang Rai: Which is the Better Option for Living and Visiting in Northern Thailand?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/chiang-mai-vs-chiang-rai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/chiang-mai-vs-chiang-rai/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When it comes to choosing between Chiang Mai and Chiang Rai in northern Thailand, many people find themselves torn between these two beautiful cities. Both have their own unique charm and attractions, but it can be difficult to determine which is the better option. In this article, we will analyze the pros and cons of both Chiang Mai and Chiang Rai to help you make an informed decision. So, whether you are considering living or visiting, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DON&#39;T SUPPORT ANIMAL EXPLOITATION! (Punta Cana, Dominican Republic)</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sea-conditions-punta-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sea-conditions-punta-cana/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will share our firsthand experience of visiting Punta Cana, Dominican Republic, and shed light on a concerning issue that we encountered. We had high hopes for an exciting day of snorkeling with sharks and stingrays, but what we encountered left us feeling disgusted and disappointed. We want to raise awareness about the mistreatment of animals in this tourist activity and urge travelers to refrain from supporting such exploitative practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is TULUM SEAWEED Ruining Your Beach Experience? Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-beaches-seaweed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-beaches-seaweed/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to Tulum and wondering if the seaweed situation will ruin your beach experience? In this article, we will explore the current state of Tulum beaches, the impact of seaweed, and what you can expect during your visit. So, whether you&amp;rsquo;re a first-time traveler or a seasoned Tulum-goer, keep reading to find out everything you need to know!
For those unfamiliar with Tulum, it is a popular beach destination in Mexico known for its pristine sandy shores and crystal-clear waters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs. Puerto Vallarta: A Comprehensive Comparison of Mexico&#39;s Top Destinations</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-vallarta-vs-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-vallarta-vs-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Mexico is known for its stunning beaches, vibrant culture, and warm hospitality. But when it comes to choosing between two popular destinations like Cancun and Puerto Vallarta, the decision can be difficult. Each side of Mexico offers its own unique features and attractions, making it important to understand the highlights of both places before making a choice. In this article, we will compare Cancun and Puerto Vallarta in great detail, so you can make an informed decision about which side of Mexico is better suited for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 24 HOURS ON COZUMEL ISLAND MEXICO: A Dog-Friendly Paradise</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-seaweed-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-seaweed-problem/</guid>
      <description>Overview Cozumel Island, located just off the coast of Playa Del Carmen in Mexico, is a hidden gem for dog owners and travelers alike. In this article, we will explore the dog-friendly paradise that is Cozumel Island, discussing the island&amp;rsquo;s attractions, activities, and amenities that make it a must-visit destination for dog lovers. From beautiful beaches to delicious food, Cozumel Island offers a variety of experiences for everyone, including your furry friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Everything You NEED TO KNOW About Visiting the US Virgin Islands</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/us-virgin-islands-vs-puerto-rico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/us-virgin-islands-vs-puerto-rico/</guid>
      <description>The US Virgin Islands, consisting of three main islands - St. Thomas, St. John, and St. Croix, offer visitors a stunning tropical paradise to explore. In this article, we will delve into the key points you need to know before visiting these beautiful islands.
Island Geography The US Virgin Islands comprise three main islands, St. Thomas, St. John, and St. Croix. St. Thomas and St. John are located close to each other, with St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hitchhiking Across South America: A Winter Adventure</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hitchhiking-south-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hitchhiking-south-america/</guid>
      <description>In this exciting adventure, Matheson Brown sets out to hitchhike across South America in just 30 days with only $10. Join him as he embarks on a thrilling journey, facing challenges, braving the elements, and relying on the kindness of strangers. In this article, we will explore the highlights and difficulties of his trip and take a closer look at the art of hitchhiking.
The Journey Begins Matheson and his travel companion start their journey in Northern California, where they plan to hitchhike all the way up to Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Naples &amp; Marco Island: Discover the Paradise Coast of Southwest Florida</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naples-or-marco-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naples-or-marco-island/</guid>
      <description>Nestled along the coast of Southwest Florida, Naples and Marco Island have long been known as the Paradise Coast. With stunning beaches, vibrant nature, and a wealth of recreational activities, these destinations have become a mecca for tourists from around the world. From exploring the waterways to indulging in shopping and dining, there is something for everyone in this coastal paradise.
A Brief History When surveyors first sailed down the bay in Southwest Florida 140 years ago, they saw the potential for a town built on tourism and commerce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **THE MARCO ISLAND TRAVEL GUIDE (2023) | Discover the Best Time to Visit this Florida Island Beach Town**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/best-time-to-visit-marco-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/best-time-to-visit-marco-island/</guid>
      <description>Marco Island is a breathtaking destination located in Florida that offers a variety of activities and attractions for visitors to enjoy. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a relaxing beach vacation or an adventure-filled getaway, Marco Island has something to offer. In this travel guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the best time to visit Marco Island, the must-see attractions, and the top things to do during your stay.
When is the Best Time to Visit Marco Island?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sargassum Seaweed: A Growing Concern for Beaches in Florida, Mexico, and the Caribbean</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-is-the-sargassum-in-cozumel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-is-the-sargassum-in-cozumel/</guid>
      <description>The presence of sargassum seaweed on beaches in Florida, Mexico, and the Caribbean has become a major issue, spreading over large stretches of the Atlantic Ocean. This article explores how the growth of sargassum seaweed is impacting marine life, the connection between its growth and chemical changes in the environment, and the efforts being made to address this problem.
The Rise of Sargassum Seaweed Sargassum seaweed has been present in the ocean for as long as humans have been exploring it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WHICH IS BETTER? Bora Bora vs. Maldives: The Ultimate Beach Vacation Showdown</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/maldives-vs-bora-bora-vs-fiji/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/maldives-vs-bora-bora-vs-fiji/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you dreaming of the perfect beach vacation but can&amp;rsquo;t decide between Bora Bora and the Maldives? Look no further! In this article, we will compare these two tropical destinations in great detail, breaking down the pros and cons of each and sharing our personal favorite. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re interested in location, accommodation, culture, price, or things to do, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered.
Location Comparison Bora Bora is situated in French Polynesia, in the South Pacific, just north of Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why Tulum, Mexico Falls Short - Problems of Violence, Sewage, and Income Inequality</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-sargassum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-sargassum/</guid>
      <description>Tulum, a popular beach town located on the East Coast of Mexico, is known for its clear turquoise waters, white sand, and ancient Mayan ruins. However, despite its attractions, there are numerous problems that make it an undesirable destination for living. In this article, we will explore the top 10 reasons why Tulum falls short, including issues such as profit over people, beach access limitations, transportation challenges, water pollution, excessive trash, land ownership disputes, seaweed problems, drug-related violence, high costs, and the prevalence of Instagrammers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gulf Shores vs Panama City Beach: Which Beach Destination is Right for You?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/pensacola-vs-panama-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/pensacola-vs-panama-city/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to the Gulf Coast and trying to decide between Gulf Shores and Panama City Beach? Both destinations offer stunning beaches, fun activities, and beautiful landscapes, but they each have their own unique charm. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key differences between Gulf Shores and Panama City Beach, and help you determine which one is the better fit for your vacation style.
Exploring Gulf Shores, Alabama Gulf Shores, located in southern Alabama, is a hidden gem known for its pristine beaches, charming atmosphere, and abundant outdoor activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Costa Rica Dominates Puerto Rico in Full Basketball Game at Centrobasket U17 Women&#39;s Championship 2023</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/costa-rica-or-puerto-rico/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/costa-rica-or-puerto-rico/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the U17 Women&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Center Championship, brought to you by FIBA - The Basketball Channel. In this article, we will be covering the second game of the opening day between Costa Rica and Puerto Rico. Both teams are ready to face off against each other in this highly anticipated matchup. The championship is being held at the Alexis Argüello Sports Center in Managua, Nicaragua.
Group A consists of the Dominican Republic, El Salvador, Nicaragua, and Mexico, while Group B includes Costa Rica, Guatemala, Panama, and Puerto Rico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>  Playa Del Carmen Beach Seaweed Update August 19th 2023: Current Conditions and Resort Highlights</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/seaweed-playa-del-carmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/seaweed-playa-del-carmen/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will provide you with the latest update on the seaweed (sargasso) situation in Playa Del Carmen, specifically on August 19th, 2023. The video transcript from the YouTube channel &amp;ldquo;Doctry 360&amp;rdquo; will serve as our main source of information. We will discuss the current conditions of the beaches, highlighting various resort areas along the coast. Additionally, we will provide step-by-step descriptions of the aerial views shown in the video, giving readers a comprehensive understanding of the beach conditions in Playa Del Carmen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> San Antonio vs Austin: A Comprehensive Comparison</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/san-antonio-vs.-austin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/san-antonio-vs.-austin/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into the age-old debate of San Antonio vs Austin. Both cities, located in Texas, have their unique characteristics and attractions. San Antonio and Austin are often compared due to their close proximity and vibrant culture. As licensed real estate agents, we are here to provide you with all the necessary information to make an informed decision. So, buckle up and let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the world of San Antonio and Austin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Chiang Mai Vs Chiang Rai: Which is the Better Choice for Living and Visiting in Northern Thailand?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/chiang-rai-vs-chiang-mai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/chiang-rai-vs-chiang-mai/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you considering a visit or a move to Northern Thailand and torn between Chiang Mai and Chiang Rai? Both cities offer their own unique charm and attractions, making the decision a difficult one. In this article, we will explore the pros and cons of each city, their suitability for living and visiting, and help you make an informed choice. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Chiang Mai: The Pros and Cons Chiang Mai, known as the &amp;ldquo;Rose of the North,&amp;rdquo; is a vibrant city with a lot to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Seaweed is Threatening the Pristine Beaches of Playa del Carmen</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/when-does-playa-del-carmen-get-seaweed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/when-does-playa-del-carmen-get-seaweed/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a trip to Cancun or the Riviera Maya, you need to be aware of a pressing issue that might affect your beach experience. Seaweed, specifically sargassum or sargasso, has become a major problem along the beautiful coastlines of Mexico. In this article, we will delve into what is causing the seaweed invasion, the extent of the problem, and what can be done to mitigate its impact on vacationers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Don&#39;t Move to Naples, Florida! | A Comprehensive Guide to Living in Naples</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/distance-from-naples-fl-to-sanibel-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/distance-from-naples-fl-to-sanibel-island/</guid>
      <description>Living in Naples, Florida may seem like a dream come true for many people. However, before you pack your bags and make the move, it&amp;rsquo;s important to consider the various factors that may not make it the perfect fit for everyone. In this article, we will discuss the top 10 reasons why you might want to think twice before moving to Naples, Florida.
Reason #10: Retirement Mentality
Naples, Florida is known for its strong retirement community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Everything You Need to Know About Visiting the US Virgin Islands</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/us-virgin-islands-or-puerto-rico-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/us-virgin-islands-or-puerto-rico-vacation/</guid>
      <description>The US Virgin Islands are a beautiful destination in the Caribbean that offer stunning beaches, rich history, and a relaxing island vibe. If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a vacation to the US Virgin Islands, there are a few things that you need to know before you go. In this article, we will cover everything from the geography and beaches to transportation, safety, pricing, and local cuisine. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and explore all the essentials of visiting the US Virgin Islands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cozumel, Mexico: A DIY One Day Tour - Explore the Hidden Gems</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-cozumel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-cozumel/</guid>
      <description>Cozumel, a picturesque island in Mexico, offers a perfect getaway for those seeking adventure and relaxation. In this article, we will take you on a virtual tour of Cozumel and provide you with valuable insights and tips for planning your own one-day tour. From transportation options to hidden beaches and local eateries, we have it all covered!
Ultramar or Windjet: Choosing the Right Boat When traveling from Playa Del Carmen to Cozumel, there are two popular boat options available: Ultramar and Windjet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CU17M 2023 Resumen: Costa Rica vs Puerto Rico - A Thrilling Match</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-vs-costa-rica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-vs-costa-rica/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will take a detailed look at the thrilling match between Costa Rica and Puerto Rico in the CU17M 2023 tournament. The game took place at the National Stadium in Guatemala City, as part of the Concacaf Under 17 Championship. Both teams were vying for a spot in the quarterfinals, making this an intense and highly anticipated match.
The Opening Whistle - Costa Rica vs Puerto Rico As the opening whistle blew, the excitement on the field was palpable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Punta Cana Seaweed Problem: How it Could Affect Your Vacation in 2023</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-dominican-republic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-dominican-republic/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a vacation to Punta Cana in 2023, there&amp;rsquo;s an issue you need to be aware of - a massive seaweed problem. This seaweed, known as sargassum, is causing concern as it makes its way through the Atlantic Ocean towards the shores of Punta Cana. With an estimated weight of three million tons, equivalent to over 400,000 elephants, it&amp;rsquo;s set to have a significant impact on the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs. Tulum vs. Cozumel: A Comprehensive Guide to the Mexican Caribbean</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-better-than-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-better-than-tulum/</guid>
      <description>The Mexican Caribbean is home to three incredible cities: Cancun, Tulum, and Cozumel. Each of these destinations offers its own unique charm and attractions, making it difficult to decide which one to visit. In this article, we will delve into the key points and details of each city to help you make an informed decision for your upcoming vacation.
Excursions and Activities When it comes to activities and excursions, Cancun takes the lead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dominican Republic vs. Puerto Rico: A Comprehensive Comparison</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-vs-cancun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-vs-cancun/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to planning a vacation in the Caribbean, two popular destinations that often come to mind are the Dominican Republic and Puerto Rico. These neighboring islands have their own unique charm and attractions that lure visitors back year after year. If you&amp;rsquo;re torn between these two beautiful countries, this side-by-side comparison will help you decide which location suits you best. From getting there to resorts, beaches, dining, nightlife, and activities, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover everything you need to know in order to make an informed decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Playa Del Carmen Vs. Cancun: Choosing the Perfect Destination for Your Family Vacation 🇲🇽</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-or-cancun-for-families/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-or-cancun-for-families/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to planning a family vacation in Mexico, Playa Del Carmen and Cancun are two popular destinations that offer unique experiences. In this article, we will compare these two locations in terms of their vibes, ease of navigation, beaches, and overall suitability for families. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re wondering whether to choose Playa Del Carmen or Cancun for your next family trip, read on to make an informed decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Punta Cana Seaweed Problem 2023: Will it Ruin Your Vacation?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-there-seaweed-in-cap-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-there-seaweed-in-cap-cana/</guid>
      <description>The beautiful beaches of Punta Cana, a popular tourist destination in the Dominican Republic, are facing a major challenge in the form of a massive seaweed bloom. A seaweed blob, twice the width of the US, is currently making its way through the Atlantic Ocean towards Punta Cana. It is estimated that three million tons of seaweed, equivalent to over 400,000 elephants in weight, will enter the region this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Seaweed Sargassum in Jamaica: Impact and Solutions | TVJ All Angles - July 6, 2022</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-in-montego-bay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-in-montego-bay/</guid>
      <description>Seaweed Sargassum, also known as floating sargassum seaweed, has become a major problem in Jamaica and other countries in the Caribbean. In this edition of TVJ All Angles, we delve into the issue and explore the impact of this seaweed on the environment and local communities.
Introduction Seaweed Sargassum has been causing havoc in the Caribbean region for the past decade. We speak to experts and professionals to understand the severity of the problem and find out if there are any feasible solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why Milos is the Must Visit Island in Greece: A Hidden Gem</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/milos-or-naxos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/milos-or-naxos/</guid>
      <description>Explore the Unique and Underrated Beauty of Milos Milos, also known as the &amp;ldquo;Island of Colors,&amp;rdquo; is a hidden gem in Greece that should be at the top of your travel bucket list. Situated in the Aegean Sea, this island is known for its stunning landscape filled with rich volcanic minerals, creating a mesmerizing display of white, pink, and orange cliffs. The contrast between the dreamlike coastline and the crystal-clear turquoise waters is a sight to behold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Exploring Lake Travis: A Memorable Bachelorette Party in Austin, Texas</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/lake-travis-bachelorette-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/lake-travis-bachelorette-party/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you ready for an unforgettable bachelorette party experience? Join us in this ultimate guide to hosting the perfect bachelorette party at Lake Travis in Austin, Texas. From stunning decorations to exciting activities, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. So grab your girls and get ready for a weekend of fun and celebration!
Setting the Scene: The Arrival Our adventure begins with the arrival at our stunning Airbnb in Austin. Decorations are in full swing as we prepare to welcome the bride-to-be and her entourage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun, Playa del Carmen, and Cozumel: Comparing Places to Live in Quintana Roo</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-vs-cozumel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-vs-cozumel/</guid>
      <description>Living in Mexico can be a dream come true for many people. The beautiful beaches, vibrant culture, and affordable lifestyle make it an attractive destination for expats. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering a move to Mexico, there are a few places you might want to consider: Cancun, Playa del Carmen, and Cozumel. In this article, we will compare these three popular destinations and help you decide which one is the best fit for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Playa del Carmen to Cozumel in Mexico: The Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-or-cozumel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-or-cozumel/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a trip to Mexico and are interested in exploring the beautiful island of Cozumel, you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat. In this article, we will guide you through everything you need to know about traveling from Playa del Carmen to Cozumel, ensuring a smooth and enjoyable journey.
Introduction to Playa del Carmen and Cozumel Playa del Carmen, located on the eastern coast of Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Yucatan Peninsula, is a popular tourist destination known for its stunning beaches, vibrant nightlife, and delicious cuisine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Punta Cana Seaweed Problem 2023: Will it Ruin Your Vacation?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-there-a-seaweed-problem-at-cap-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-there-a-seaweed-problem-at-cap-cana/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Are you planning a vacation to Punta Cana in 2023? Well, you may want to be aware of a potential issue that could affect your beach experience. There is a growing concern about a massive seaweed problem heading towards Punta Cana. In this article, we will explore the seaweed issue, its causes, and how it might impact your vacation. We will also provide you with some helpful resources to track the seaweed situation and make informed decisions about your trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> San Antonio vs Austin | A Detailed Guide to Help You Choose the Perfect Vacation Destination</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/san-antonio-vs.-austin-for-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/san-antonio-vs.-austin-for-vacation/</guid>
      <description>Are you torn between visiting San Antonio or Austin for your next vacation? Both cities offer unique experiences and attractions that make them popular tourist destinations. But how do you decide which one is right for you? In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll compare the two cities in terms of population, housing, cost of living, and entertainment to help you make an informed decision. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Population and Size San Antonio, with a population of approximately 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Is Panama City Beach Florida a Good Place to Live in 2023?**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-destin-far-enough-away-from-panama-city-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-destin-far-enough-away-from-panama-city-beach/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Panama City Beach, Florida is known for its beautiful sandy beaches and affordable coastal living. But is it a good place to live in 2023? In this article, we will explore the pros and cons of living in Panama City Beach, and analyze why it may or may not be a desirable place to call home.
The Beauty of Panama City Beach One of the undeniable facts about Panama City Beach is its physical beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Florida Trip to Sarasota, Naples, Tampa, and St. Petersburg: Exploring the Sunshine State</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/traveling-from-sarasota-fl-to-naples-fl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/traveling-from-sarasota-fl-to-naples-fl/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Planning a trip to Florida? Look no further! In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll take you on a virtual journey to some of the most beautiful destinations in the Sunshine State. From the vibrant city of Tampa to the breathtaking beaches of Sarasota, Naples, and St. Petersburg, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore it all. Pack your bags and get ready for an adventure-filled vacation.
Arriving in Tampa Bay: A Memorable Start Our Florida adventure begins in Tampa Bay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 12 Essential Tips for an Unforgettable Family Vacation in Costa Rica</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hawaii-or-costa-rica-for-family-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hawaii-or-costa-rica-for-family-vacation/</guid>
      <description>Costa Rica is a captivating country located in Central America, known for its natural beauty, biodiversity, and adventure activities. As a seasoned traveler who has visited Costa Rica numerous times, I want to share with you some essential tips to ensure that your family vacation in Costa Rica is a truly unforgettable experience. From planning your itinerary to enjoying the incredible wildlife and stunning beaches, here are 12 tips that will make your trip to Costa Rica truly memorable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Tulum Seaweed Ruining Your Beach Experience? Exploring the Reality of Tulum&#39;s Seaweed Situation</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/seaweed-at-tulum-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/seaweed-at-tulum-beach/</guid>
      <description>Tulum, Mexico is known for its stunning beaches and crystal-clear waters, but lately, there has been a growing concern about the amount of seaweed found along the shoreline. Travelers are wondering if the seaweed will ruin their beach experience. In this article, we will delve into the current state of Tulum&amp;rsquo;s seaweed situation, its impact on beach activities, and provide valuable insights to help you plan your Tulum vacation accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Myrtle Beach, SC vs Virginia Beach, VA: A Clash of East Coast Beaches</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/north-myrtle-beach-sc-to-virginia-beach-va/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/north-myrtle-beach-sc-to-virginia-beach-va/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a beach enthusiast on the East Coast, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably wondered about the differences between Myrtle Beach, SC, and Virginia Beach, VA. These two iconic destinations are known for their stunning shorelines, vibrant atmospheres, and endless activities. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive deep into the comparison between these two vacation hotspots and help you decide which one is right for you and your family.
Myrtle Beach, SC: Nostalgia and Familiarity As a travel destination, Myrtle Beach holds a special place in the hearts of many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Spring Break Vlog in Naples, Florida - College Trip 2022</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naples-spring-break-resorts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naples-spring-break-resorts/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready for an unforgettable college spring break trip? Join Emma Martinson on her exciting adventure in Naples, Florida in 2022. In this vlog, Emma takes you through her daily activities, from exploring the hotel to enjoying the beautiful beaches and trying out delicious food. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for travel inspiration or just want to experience the fun and excitement of a college spring break, keep reading!
Checking into the Hotel Emma starts her vlog by checking into their hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why You Should Visit Isla Mujeres, Mexico: A Beautiful Caribbean Getaway</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/isla-mujeres-live-cam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/isla-mujeres-live-cam/</guid>
      <description>Isla Mujeres, a stunning Caribbean island located just off the coast of Cancun, Mexico, is a must-visit destination for travelers seeking crystal clear waters and breathtaking views. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the beauty of Isla Mujeres and the unique experiences it offers to its visitors.
A Scenic Breakfast with a View Start your day at Kinha, a restaurant with sweeping views of the Caribbean. Enjoy a delicious &amp;ldquo;build your own&amp;rdquo; omelette and take in the beauty of the turquoise and blue waters that surround you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs Tulum vs Cozumel: Which is the Best Destination for Your Mexican Caribbean Getaway?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-ou-cozumel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-ou-cozumel/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to the Mexican Caribbean but can&amp;rsquo;t decide between Cancun, Tulum, and Cozumel? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. After visiting all three cities, we can confidently say that each one offers something unique and amazing. In this article, we will compare and contrast these destinations across five different categories to help you make an informed decision about where to spend your vacation. From excursions and beaches to transportation, prices, and food, we will cover it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Playa Del Carmen Beach Seaweed Update: August 19th, 2023</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-seaweed-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-seaweed-season/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s sargasso update for Playa Del Carmen&amp;rsquo;s beaches. It is Saturday, August 19th, 2023, and I am here to provide you with the latest information on the current seaweed situation. As I reflect on the past year, I realize that I have been bringing these reports to you for over a year now. If you find these updates helpful, you can show your support by visiting buy me a coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Playa del Carmen to Cozumel in Mexico: The Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-or-playa-del-carmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-or-playa-del-carmen/</guid>
      <description>If you find yourself in Playa del Carmen, Mexico, and are looking for a day trip to a nearby island, Cozumel is an excellent choice. Playa del Carmen offers easy access to Cozumel, making it a popular destination for tourists. In this definitive guide, we will explore how to travel from Playa del Carmen to Cozumel, what to expect during the journey, and what awaits you on this beautiful Caribbean island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Punta Cana Sargassum Problem 2023: Will it Ruin Your Vacation?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/punta-cana-sargassum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/punta-cana-sargassum/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Punta Cana, a popular tourist destination in the Dominican Republic, is facing a significant challenge in 2023. A massive seaweed blob, twice the width of the US, is making its way through the Atlantic Ocean towards Punta Cana. With an expected weight of three million tons, equivalent to over 400,000 elephants, this influx of seaweed is a cause for concern. In this article, we will explore the sargassum problem in Punta Cana, its origins, the impact on tourism, and how to plan your vacation accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>  Flat Earth Curvature Experiment: Naples Pier to Sanibel Island</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/distance-sanibel-island-to-naples/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/distance-sanibel-island-to-naples/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore a video transcript discussing a flat earth curvature experiment conducted from Naples Pier to Sanibel Island. The experiment aimed to determine if there was any sign of curvature, which is believed to prove that the Earth is round. The video provides valuable insights for individuals living in the area and invites them to observe the evidence for themselves. We will delve into the key points discussed in the transcript, including the formula for curvature, the measurement of distances using Google Maps, and the importance of focusing on the core debate in the flat earth community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs. Puerto Vallarta Mexico: Comparing the Best Sides of Mexico</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/que-es-mejor-cancun-o-puerto-vallarta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/que-es-mejor-cancun-o-puerto-vallarta/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a vacation to Mexico but can&amp;rsquo;t decide between Puerto Vallarta and the Cancun side, this article is here to help! Both destinations offer stunning features, but they have their own unique highlights. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll compare the major attractions, prices, weather, activities, and accommodations in Puerto Vallarta and the Cancun/Riviera Maya side. By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a better understanding of which side is better suited for your vacation preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tulum vs Playa del Carmen: A Comprehensive Comparison for Travelers</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-vs-playa-del-carmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-vs-playa-del-carmen/</guid>
      <description>When planning a trip to Mexico&amp;rsquo;s stunning Riviera Maya, it can be tough to choose between two popular destinations: Tulum and Playa del Carmen. Each has its own unique charm and attractions, making the decision even more difficult. But fear not, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help you decide by providing a comprehensive comparison of Tulum and Playa del Carmen.
Location and Beach Accessibility One of the key factors when choosing a destination is the accessibility to the beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Palm Springs Travel Guide: Everything You Need to Know**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/distance-between-palm-springs-and-palm-desert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/distance-between-palm-springs-and-palm-desert/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to Palm Springs, California? Look no further! In this comprehensive travel guide, we will provide you with all the information you need to know before you go. From getting in and getting around, to what to see, eat, and do, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and explore the beautiful city of Palm Springs.
A Brief Introduction to Palm Springs Before we begin, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the background of Palm Springs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **What to Know About Tulum, Mexico! A Complete Guide**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-is-the-ocean-water-in-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-is-the-ocean-water-in-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Tulum, Mexico is a destination known for its stunning beaches, rich history, and vibrant culture. Located on the eastern coast of the Yucatan Peninsula, Tulum offers visitors a unique blend of natural beauty and ancient ruins. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking to relax on the pristine white sand beaches, explore ancient Mayan ruins, or indulge in delicious cuisine, Tulum has something for everyone. In this guide, we will take you through everything you need to know about Tulum, Mexico, including its ocean water, attractions, and activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SAN ANTONIO VS AUSTIN: EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/san-antonio-or-austin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/san-antonio-or-austin/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore the differences between the cities of San Antonio and Austin. Both cities are located in Texas, but they have their own unique characteristics that set them apart. From population and housing to entertainment and food, we will discuss everything you need to know about these two vibrant cities.
Population and Size San Antonio has a population of approximately 1.4 million people as of 2020, while Austin has around 945,000 residents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Best Beaches near Orlando: Clearwater, Cocoa Beach, Daytona Beach, and Anna Maria</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cocoa-beach-versus-daytona/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cocoa-beach-versus-daytona/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to Orlando, Florida and want to include a visit to the beach? While Orlando itself doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a beach, there are several beautiful options just a short drive away. In this article, we will explore the best beaches near Orlando, their distance from the city, and what makes each one unique. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a quiet getaway or a bustling beach with plenty of activities, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CNL 2023 British Virgin Islands vs Puerto Rico | Exciting Highlights of a Thrilling Match</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-vs-us-virgin-islands/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-vs-us-virgin-islands/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In an exciting yet captivating match, the British Virgin Islands (BVI) clashed against Puerto Rico in the CNL 2023 tournament. Both teams displayed their skills and determination as they fought for victory on the field. This article will provide a detailed account of the highlights from this thrilling match, including the goals, opportunities, and standout moments.
Key Points First Half Action
In the early stages, BVI showed their attacking prowess as they sent a dangerous ball into the area, leading to a penalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Comprehensive Guide to Exploring Tybee Island: A Gem on the East Coast</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tybee-island-to-hilton-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tybee-island-to-hilton-head/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Discovering the Charms of Tybee Island Tybee Island, a charming barrier island spanning 3.36 square miles, is located just 18 miles east of Savannah. In this quick tour, we will explore the captivating beauty and unique features of this small town, offering an abundance of activities and attractions for visitors. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re seeking relaxation on its pristine sandy beaches, immersing yourself in history, or indulging in sumptuous seafood, Tybee Island has something for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Best Time to Visit Tybee Island - A Guide to Planning Your Trip</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/best-time-of-year-to-go-to-tybee-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/best-time-of-year-to-go-to-tybee-island/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you planning a trip to Tybee Island? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! In this article, we will share with you the best time to visit Tybee Island, along with all the important details you need to know to plan your trip effectively. So, get ready to explore this beautiful coastal destination in Georgia.
When to Visit Tybee Island The best time to visit Tybee Island depends on your preferences and what you want to do during your trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Destin and Panama City Beach: A Guide to Florida&#39;s Beautiful Emerald Coast</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/destin-to-panama-city-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/destin-to-panama-city-beach/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a beach vacation destination in Florida, look no further than Destin and Panama City Beach. These two stunning coastal towns are located in what is known as the Emerald Coast, named for its sparkling emerald-green waters and pristine white sand beaches. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at these two destinations and explore some of the highlights and attractions that make them so popular among tourists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Greece Vacation Vlog ~ Exploring Crete, Santorini &amp; Mykonos</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/mykonos-vs-crete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/mykonos-vs-crete/</guid>
      <description>In this Greece vacation vlog, Angie takes us on a journey through her 12-day trip to Crete, Santorini, and Mykonos. She shares her experiences, highlights, and recommendations from her once in a lifetime trip. From stunning landscapes to delicious cuisine, Greece has a lot to offer. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details of this incredible adventure.
Exploring Crete: The First Stop Angie and her two daughters began their Greece trip by flying into Athens, followed by a short flight to Crete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SAN ANTONIO VS AUSTIN: EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/austin-or-san-antonio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/austin-or-san-antonio/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the age-old debate of San Antonio versus Austin. Both cities have their own unique charm and character, and it can be challenging to choose between the two. As licensed real estate agents and experts in the field, we will provide you with all the necessary information to make an informed decision. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details of what each city has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tulum or Playa del Carmen: Which is the Better Vacation Spot?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-or-cancun-or-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-or-cancun-or-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Are you torn between choosing Tulum or Playa del Carmen as your vacation destination? Both locations offer unique experiences, but understanding the differences can help you make an informed decision. In this article, we will explore the key points of each destination and help you decide which one is right for you.
Getting Around in Playa del Carmen Playa del Carmen is designed to be efficient and easily navigable for tourists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Best Time to Visit Hawaii: Ideal Weather, Smaller Crowds, and Lower Prices Revealed</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hawaii-trip-vs-virgin-islands-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hawaii-trip-vs-virgin-islands-cost/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Are you planning a trip to Hawaii but not sure when is the best time to visit? In this article, we will analyze the three C&amp;rsquo;s—cost, clouds, and crowds—to determine the optimal time to visit Hawaii. We have done extensive research and gathered data from reputable sources such as NOAA, weather.com, and the Hawaii Tourism Authority to provide you with accurate information. If you want to make the most of your Hawaii vacation, read on as we reveal why October is the ideal month to visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Guide to Isla Holbox, Mexico: A Remote Riviera Maya Destination</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/holbox-marine-forecast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/holbox-marine-forecast/</guid>
      <description>Isla Holbox, located on the North Coast of the Yucatan Peninsula in Mexico, offers a remote getaway known for its stunning beaches and laid-back atmosphere. In this ultimate guide, we will explore the top things to see and do in Isla Holbox, how to get there, the best times to visit, as well as discuss the pros and cons of this hidden gem.
Getting to Isla Holbox Getting to Isla Holbox can be a bit of a journey, but the idyllic destination is well worth it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SAN ANTONIO VS AUSTIN: A Comprehensive Comparison</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/austin-vs-san-antonio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/austin-vs-san-antonio/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into the must-know details about the vibrant cities of San Antonio and Austin. These two cities have often been compared due to their proximity and unique characteristics. As licensed real estate agents and inhabitants of the Alamo City, Jonathan and Trevor from Alamo City Living bring us all the relevant information we need to make an informed decision about choosing between these two cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Costa Rica vs Puerto Rico: U17 Women&#39;s Basketball Championship 2023</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/costa-rica-vs-puerto-rico/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/costa-rica-vs-puerto-rico/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the U17 Women&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Center Championship transmission brought to you by de Nica Sport, the official YouTube channel. In this article, we will be discussing the second game of the opening day between Costa Rica and Puerto Rico. Both teams are competing in Group B along with Guatemala and Panama.
Before the game, both teams were seen practicing and warming up at the Alexis Argüello sports center in Managua, Nicaragua.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Why We Chose Naxos Over Mykonos and Santorini: Exploring the Greek Island of Naxos**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naxos-or-mykonos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naxos-or-mykonos/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the beautiful Greek island of Naxos! In this article, we will take you on a virtual tour of Naxos, a hidden gem among the popular Greek islands of Mykonos and Santorini. Join Mr. and Mrs. Adventure as they share their experiences and adventures on this stunning island.
Naxos: The Largest, Greenest, and Most Diverse Island in the Cyclades Naxos, known for its lush greenery and diverse landscapes, is the largest island in the Cyclades archipelago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Head-to-Head: Sarasota Vs Naples Florida - Which Should You Pick?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sarasota-vs-naples/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sarasota-vs-naples/</guid>
      <description>Are you deciding between Sarasota and Naples as your future home in Florida? Look no further, as we compare these two cities to help you make an informed decision. This article will explore the value proposition of each city, highlighting their strengths and key differences. Stay tuned until the end to find out whether Sarasota or Naples is the right choice for you.
Sarasota: A City on the Gulf Coast Sarasota, located in Sarasota County, is a city on the Gulf Coast of Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> San Antonio vs Austin: A Comprehensive Comparison</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/do-you-like-austin-or-san-antonio-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/do-you-like-austin-or-san-antonio-better/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into the much-debated topic of San Antonio vs Austin. Both cities have their own unique characteristics and attractions, and we will explore them in detail. As experts in the field of real estate and living in San Antonio, we have firsthand knowledge of the intricacies of these two Texas cities. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the comparison and find out everything you need to know about San Antonio and Austin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Flight Experience: Air Tahiti Takes You to Bora Bora</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/bora-bora-hawaii/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/bora-bora-hawaii/</guid>
      <description>Flying through paradise has never been more breathtaking than with Air Tahiti. Offering inter-island flights to beautiful destinations like Bora Bora, this airline ensures a truly remarkable experience. In this article, we will delve into the details of an extraordinary flight with Air Tahiti, exploring the unique features of their service and the stunning views passengers can expect along the way.
Experiencing Air Tahiti&amp;rsquo;s Inter-Island Milk Run When boarding the flight to Bora Bora, passengers are greeted with open seating options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>  Fort Myers vs Naples: A Comprehensive Comparison of Two Southwest Florida Cities</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/fort-myers-vs-fort-lauderdale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/fort-myers-vs-fort-lauderdale/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The cities of Fort Myers and Naples are two major cities located along the Gulf Coast of Florida. They are known for their beautiful beaches, vibrant communities, and desirable lifestyles. However, many people wonder which city is better suited for their needs and preferences. In this article, we will delve into the similarities and differences between Fort Myers and Naples, exploring various factors such as location, weather, affordability, population, traffic, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Massive Waves of Toxic Seaweed Threaten Cozumel: A Crisis for the Yucatan Peninsula</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-seaweed-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-seaweed-2019/</guid>
      <description>Seaweed has become a major problem for the pristine beaches and crystal-clear waters of the Caribbean. The Yucatan Peninsula, including popular destinations like Cancun and Cozumel, has been hit hard by massive waves of seaweed called Sargassum. This phenomenon, which is the largest algae bloom in the world, poses a threat to the local economies, ecosystems, and even human health.
The Yucatan Peninsula is a tourism hotspot, with millions of visitors from the US, Europe, and Canada flocking to its beaches every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Seaweed Invasion: A Growing Threat to Playa del Carmen&#39;s Pristine Beaches</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-beaches-seaweed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-beaches-seaweed/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a trip to Cancun or anywhere along the Riviera Maya, there&amp;rsquo;s an important issue you need to be aware of – the seaweed invasion. In recent years, Playa del Carmen&amp;rsquo;s iconic beaches have been plagued by a phenomenon known as sargassum, a type of seaweed that has become a major problem during the summer months. In this article, we will delve into the causes behind this seaweed invasion, the impact it has on the region, and what can be done to address this growing threat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Visit Hilton Head SC and Tybee Island GA: A Vacationers&#39; Paradise</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-far-is-hilton-head-from-tybee-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-far-is-hilton-head-from-tybee-island/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Where in the world is Frank and Gina, your go-to channel for travel inspiration and destination reviews. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll be exploring the beautiful Marriott Hilton Resort in Hilton Head, South Carolina, as well as the charming Tybee Island in Georgia. So sit back, relax, and let&amp;rsquo;s embark on a virtual tour of these two captivating locations.
Hilton Head South Carolina: A Coastal Haven Located off the coast of South Carolina, Hilton Head is a favorite destination for tourists from neighboring states like Georgia, Florida, North Carolina, and Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Where to Scuba Dive in Cozumel: The Ultimate Dive Guide</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/diving-in-cancun-vs-cozumel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/diving-in-cancun-vs-cozumel/</guid>
      <description>Cozumel is a paradise for scuba diving enthusiasts, with its crystal-clear waters and stunning reefs. If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a scuba diving trip to Cozumel and are unsure where to dive, look no further. In this guide, we will explore the two diving options available in Cozumel: shore diving and boat diving.
Shore Diving: Affordable Exploration of Local Reefs and Habitats If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a more affordable option and want to explore the local reefs and habitats, shore diving is the way to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ** Playa Del Carmen Beach Update August 19th, 2023: Current State of Seaweed and Beach Resorts**</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-seaweed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-seaweed/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the latest update on the state of Playa Del Carmen&amp;rsquo;s beaches in terms of seaweed presence. As an expert in providing accurate and up-to-date information, I have been delivering these reports to you for over a year now. If you find these updates helpful, feel free to support my work by making a donation or special request at buy me a coffee.com.
The Current Situation As we dive into today&amp;rsquo;s report, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Playa Del Carmen is currently experiencing improved conditions compared to the same time last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs. Cozumel vs. Playa del Carmen: Comparing Places to Live in Quintana Roo</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-vs-riviera-maya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-vs-riviera-maya/</guid>
      <description>Moving to Mexico? Considering options for your new home in Quintana Roo? Look no further! In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll compare three popular destinations: Cancun, Cozumel, and Playa del Carmen. Each place has its own unique charm and advantages, so let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and find out which one suits you best!
Cancun: The Vibrant Tourist Hub Cancun is undoubtedly the most famous destination on our list. As a bustling tourist hub, it boasts a wide range of amenities, including numerous hotels, resorts, hospitals, and dentists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Flat Earth Curvature Experiment: Examining the Distance from Naples Pier to Sanibel Island</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naples-to-sanibel-island-distance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naples-to-sanibel-island-distance/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into a fascinating flat earth curvature experiment conducted by a flat-earth enthusiast known as MinnesotaFlats. The experiment aims to test the curvature of the Earth by examining the distance between Naples Pier and Sanibel Island in Florida. Through this experiment, we will explore the evidence presented and analyze its implications for the flat-earth theory.
Step 1: Setting the Scene MinnesotaFlats starts the experiment by explaining his objective, which is to observe Sanibel Island from Naples Pier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Tulum Seaweed Damaging Your Beach Experience?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-beaches-algae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/tulum-beaches-algae/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Tulum is known for its stunning beaches and crystal-clear waters, but recently, the presence of seaweed has become a concern for many travelers. In this article, we will delve into the issue of seaweed in Tulum, discussing its impact on the beach experience and providing valuable insights for those planning to visit. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned Tulum traveler or a first-timer, read on to find out everything you need to know about this natural phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Puerto Rico to St. Croix: Exploring Rainforests, Sailing, and Having Fun!</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-to-st-croix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/puerto-rico-to-st-croix/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to Jetty the Gypsy&amp;rsquo;s Dog Vlog! In this exciting episode, we&amp;rsquo;re taking you on a thrilling journey from Puerto Rico to St. Croix. Get ready for a thrilling adventure filled with rainforest hikes, sailing on the beautiful Puerto Rican coast, and discovering the wonders of St. Croix. Join us as we explore these beautiful destinations and create unforgettable memories. So buckle up and let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Hiking in the Puerto Rican Rainforest Our first stop takes us to the lush Puerto Rican rainforest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sargassum Project Underway: Finding Commercial Solutions for St. Lucia&#39;s Seaweed Problem</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/st-lucia-sargassum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/st-lucia-sargassum/</guid>
      <description>Introduction St. Lucia is taking proactive steps to address the challenges posed by the excessive accumulation of sargassum seaweed along its picturesque coastlines. Since 2011, the Caribbean region has been facing periodic influxes of sargassum, leading to significant economic losses and adverse effects on the environment and human health. However, the government of St. Lucia, in collaboration with the Caribbean Regional Fisheries Mechanism and the New Zealand Institute of Plant and Food Research, is embarking on a project to determine suitable commercial products that can be derived from sargassum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Sargassum Is Affecting Mexico&#39;s Stunning Beaches: An In-Depth Look at the Seaweed Problem Along the Riviera Maya</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-in-tulum-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-in-tulum-right-now/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a trip to Cancun or exploring the Riviera Maya, there&amp;rsquo;s an important issue you need to be aware of: the invasion of Sargassum seaweed. This once harmless seaweed has become a major nuisance, turning pristine beaches into unpleasant sights. In this article, we will delve into the causes of this problem and provide you with some examples of how it is affecting different areas along the Riviera Maya in June 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Naples, Florida: A Paradise Coast Gem Worth Exploring</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-naples-florida-worth-visiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-naples-florida-worth-visiting/</guid>
      <description>Naples, Florida, located in Southwest Florida, is often referred to as the &amp;ldquo;Paradise Coast&amp;rdquo; for good reason. With its 280 days of sunshine per year, beautiful beaches, wildlife sanctuaries, and vibrant art scene, Naples has become a top destination for both retirees and vacationers. In this article, we will explore some of the best things to see and do in Naples, Florida, and why it is worth visiting.
Beautiful Beaches that Never Disappoint When it comes to beaches, Florida is known for its stunning coastlines, and Naples is no exception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Costa Rica the Same as Puerto Rico? - A Concacaf Championship Match Analysis</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-costa-rica-and-puerto-rico-the-same/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-costa-rica-and-puerto-rico-the-same/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into the thrilling match between Costa Rica and Puerto Rico in the Concacaf Under 17 Championship. The game took place at the National Stadium in Guatemala City, marking Puerto Rico&amp;rsquo;s first game in Guatemala and the fourth for Costa Rica. Both teams, winners of their respective groups, were meeting in the round of 16. This encounter promised to be an exciting clash of skills and tactics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Tulum Seaweed Ruining Your Vacation? Find Out Here!</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/sargassum-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you planning a trip to Tulum and wondering if the seaweed is going to ruin your beach experience? In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the current state of Tulum&amp;rsquo;s beaches, explore the impact of seaweed on your vacation, and provide helpful tips for making the most of your time in this beautiful destination. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re ready for an adventure-filled vacation, keep reading!
Tulum Beach: Seaweed Situation Tulum Beach, known for its pristine beauty, has recently been affected by an increase in seaweed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs. Cozumel vs. Playa del Carmen: Comparing the Best Places to Live in Quintana Roo, Mexico</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-vs-playa-del-carmen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cozumel-vs-playa-del-carmen/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re considering moving to Mexico, you may have come across three popular destinations - Cancun, Cozumel, and Playa del Carmen. Each place offers unique advantages and attractions, so let&amp;rsquo;s compare them in order to help you make an informed decision about where to live in Quintana Roo.
1. Cancun - The Ultimate Tourist Destination Cancun is undoubtedly the most famous destination among the three. It is known for its vibrant tourism industry, with a plethora of hotels, resorts, and amenities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ST. CROIX USVI - A Comprehensive Guide for Visitors</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-safe-is-st-croix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-safe-is-st-croix/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Are you planning a trip to St. Croix in the US Virgin Islands? Before you go, it&amp;rsquo;s important to know some key factors that could impact your experience. In this article, we will discuss the pros and cons of visiting St. Croix, ensuring you are well-prepared for your trip. From home ownership challenges to the lack of modern conveniences, we will explore various aspects of life on the island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Visit Hilton Head South Carolina and Tybee Island Georgia: A Coastal Adventure</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-far-is-tybee-island-from-hilton-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/how-far-is-tybee-island-from-hilton-head/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the beautiful coastal destinations of Hilton Head, South Carolina, and Tybee Island, Georgia! In this article, we will take you on a virtual tour of these captivating spots and provide you with all the information you need to plan your own visit. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a nature lover, beach enthusiast, or simply seeking a relaxing getaway, these two locations have something for everyone.
As we start our journey, let&amp;rsquo;s begin with Hilton Head South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why Do Britain &amp; The U.S. Both Have Territories Called The Virgin Islands?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/british-virgin-islands-vs-us-virgin-islands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/british-virgin-islands-vs-us-virgin-islands/</guid>
      <description>An In-depth Look at the Origins and Division of the Virgin Islands
The name &amp;ldquo;Virgin Islands&amp;rdquo; may conjure up images of a tropical paradise, but its origins are actually rooted in history and mythology. In this article, we will explore the reasons behind the name and delve into the intriguing division of the Virgin Islands between Britain and the United States.
The Naming of the Virgin Islands Contrary to popular belief, the name &amp;ldquo;Virgin Islands&amp;rdquo; does not derive from the notion that the islands are inhabited solely by virgins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5 Things You Must Know Before Traveling to the Virgin Islands: St Thomas &amp; St John</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/st-croix-vs-st-thomas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/st-croix-vs-st-thomas/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to the Virgin Islands but don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start? With stunning beaches, delicious food, and plenty of activities, it can be tough to choose between the lively St Thomas and the serene St John. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll give you our expert opinions on each island, the benefits of both, and share our recommendations on how to split your time between the two. Before diving into the details, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about getting there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun vs. Puerto Vallarta Mexico: Which Side is Better for Your Dream Vacation?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-or-puerto-vallarta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/playa-del-carmen-or-puerto-vallarta/</guid>
      <description>Choosing between Puerto Vallarta and the Cancun side of Mexico can be a difficult decision. Both the Caribbean and Pacific sides of Mexico have their own unique and stunning features. In this article, we will compare the major highlights of both destinations to help you decide whether Puerto Vallarta or the Cancun/Riviera Maya area is better suited for your dream vacation.
Cancun and Riviera Maya: The Perfect Tropical All-Inclusive Getaway</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cancun Vs. Tulum: Which Beach Paradise is Right for You?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cancun-vs-tulum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/cancun-vs-tulum/</guid>
      <description>Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Riviera Maya is home to two top vacation destinations: Tulum and Cancun. If you&amp;rsquo;re planning your next beach getaway and are torn between these two cities, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help you decide. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the key differences between Cancun and Tulum, from their atmospheres and nightlife to their accommodations, travel options, and weather. By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a clearer picture of which destination aligns better with your preferences and vacation goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Best Beaches Near Orlando: Clearwater, Cocoa Beach, Daytona Beach, and Anna Maria Island</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/best-beach-daytona-or-cocoa-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/best-beach-daytona-or-cocoa-beach/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to Orlando and wondering if there are any beaches nearby? While Orlando itself doesn&amp;rsquo;t have its own beach, there are several cities close to Orlando that have beautiful beaches just a short drive away. In this article, we will explore the best beaches near Orlando and provide you with all the information you need to plan a beach day during your trip.
Why Renting a Car is Recommended Before we dive into the details of each beach, we highly recommend renting a car during your trip to Orlando.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Best Beaches near Orlando: Clearwater, Cocoa Beach, Daytona Beach, and Anna Maria</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/better-pier-cocoa-beach-or-daytona-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/better-pier-cocoa-beach-or-daytona-beach/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to Orlando and wondering if there are any beaches nearby? While Orlando itself doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a beach, there are several cities close to it that boast beautiful shorelines. In this article, we will explore the best beaches near Orlando, their distance from the city, and what makes each of them unique. So buckle up and get ready to plan the perfect beach getaway!
One of the closest beaches to Orlando is Cocoa Beach, which is just an hour away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living in San Antonio vs Living in Austin: The Ultimate Comparison Guide</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/living-in-san-antonio-vs-living-in-austin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/living-in-san-antonio-vs-living-in-austin/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Welcome to the ultimate comparison guide between San Antonio and Austin. As experts in the field of real estate and local living, we are here to provide you with all the information you need to make an informed decision. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re considering a move to San Antonio or Austin, this guide will cover everything from population statistics to housing affordability, and even the entertainment and food scenes. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and find out which city is the best fit for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Seville Spain Worth Visiting? Exploring the Beautiful City</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-seville-worth-visiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/is-seville-worth-visiting/</guid>
      <description>Seville, Spain is a city that is often overlooked by tourists when planning their European vacations. However, after experiencing the city first-hand, I can confidently say that it is an absolute must-visit destination. From stunning architecture to vibrant culture, Seville has something for everyone. In this article, I will take you through my journey in Seville and share why I believe this city is truly worth visiting.
Plaza de Espana: A Breathtaking Marvel One of the first places I visited in Seville was Plaza de Espana, and let me tell you, it was absolutely awe-inspiring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Taos New Mexico: 10 Must-See Attractions</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/taos-vs.-santa-fe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/taos-vs.-santa-fe/</guid>
      <description>Taos is a small, historic village located in the breathtaking Sangre de Cristo Mountains of North Central New Mexico. With a population of just under 6,000 people, this town is bursting with rich history and unique attractions. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a history enthusiast or a lover of natural beauty, Taos has something for everyone. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the top 10 things to do when visiting Taos and dive into the fascinating details of each attraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Vacationing in Hilton Head and Tybee Island: A Fun-Filled Adventure</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hilton-head-to-tybee-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hilton-head-to-tybee-island/</guid>
      <description>by Sarahhh Beth
Image Source: Unsplash.com
Are you ready for a thrilling vacation? Join us as we embark on a journey to the beautiful Hilton Head and Tybee Island. In this article, we will take you on an adventure-filled vacation, starting with our room tour at the Beach House in Hilton Head.
Step 1: Arriving at Hilton Head Beach House After a long and tiring journey, we finally reached our destination, the Beach House at Hilton Head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5 Things to Know Before Going to the Virgin Islands: Comparing St Thomas &amp; St John</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/compare-hawaii-to-usvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/compare-hawaii-to-usvi/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a vacation to the U.S Virgin Islands but don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start? Are you torn between spending your time on the lively St Thomas or the serene St John? In this article, we will provide you with a comprehensive comparison of both islands, highlighting the benefits of each and offering recommendations on how to divide your time between them. From the best beaches to the tastiest food, we will cover all the important aspects to consider before you embark on your Virgin Islands adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Everything You NEED TO KNOW - Visiting the US Virgin Islands</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hawaii-vs-us-virgin-islands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/hawaii-vs-us-virgin-islands/</guid>
      <description>Are you planning a trip to the US Virgin Islands? Look no further! In this comprehensive guide, we will provide you with everything you need to know before visiting this tropical paradise. From the island geography to beaches, transportation, safety, pricing, and local cuisine, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. So read on to ensure a memorable and hassle-free vacation in the US Virgin Islands!
Island Geography The US Virgin Islands consist of three main islands: St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gulf Shores vs Panama City Beach: Which Beach Destination is Perfect for You?</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/panama-city-beach-to-destin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/panama-city-beach-to-destin/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to beach vacations, two popular destinations that often come to mind are Gulf Shores and Panama City Beach. Both located in the beautiful state of Alabama, these beach towns offer stunning white sand beaches and plenty of fun activities for visitors. But which one is better suited to your vacation preferences? In this article, we will compare Gulf Shores and Panama City Beach to help you decide which beach destination is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Head-to-Head: Sarasota vs Naples Florida / Choosing Your Ideal City</title>
      <link>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naples-to-sarasota/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohitchhiking.github.io/posts/naples-to-sarasota/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you considering a move to Florida but torn between the picturesque cities of Sarasota and Naples? Look no further! In this article, we will compare the two cities in great detail, highlighting their value propositions and key differences. By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll have all the necessary information to make an informed decision on whether Sarasota or Naples is the right fit for you.
Sarasota: The Gulf Coast Gem Let&amp;rsquo;s start with Sarasota, a beautiful city located on the Gulf Coast of Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
